Open the gate.
Come on, let it in, let it in.
Wait.
- Hey...
- Huh?
- She's dead.
- Get rid of her.
Tell me, where are the rest of the girls?
- Check your phone.
- Go on, check it.
Answer your phone.
Papa!
Help me, Papa!
Papa, save me! I'm so scared, Papa!
Papa, help me!
Hi!
I'm Boss.
You know, the best thing about
being called Boss, hmm?
Even my boss calls me Boss!
Please, let my daughter go.
Quit crying already! You little girl..
Now tell me,
who gave you the information
about this place, hmm?
You don't know my boss Rao.
He will skin your daughter
- alive with a rusted blade.
- No, please.
It makes me sick.
I just got a voice note.
Rao's gang has kept the 40 missing girls
in the freezer yard in Allapuzha.
I'll give you 15 days.
Find out who it was.
Otherwise, your daughter too...
Oh no, what will happen to us now?
Someone is going to come.
Someone is definitely going
to come save us.
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
A battle is brewing
and he's gonna spare none,
Here comes, Baby John!
God, what a life I have!
Baby, I'm getting late for school!
Two minutes.
Two minutes!
You wake up late every day,
and everyday you've get me late too!
And this old bike...
don't even get me started!
You should just sell it to a museum.
Don't yell at Pinky, baby.
'Idiot, it's black, not pink!'
Babyyyyyyyyy!
Let's finish him!
Go go go. Fast!
Yes baby!
Baby, show him!
I'm on it, baby.
Yayyy!
- Ganapati Bappa... !
- Morya!
Let's go, baby!
Yayyy!
Hey, come out here!
Wait, I'm coming!
- What, huh?
- Sir! You...
- Sorry, sir.
- What sorry?
You splashed my baby,
so I had to get you wet too.
Baby seat?
You've got a kid too?
So father to father -
her ego got hurt, sir.
- Waste!
- Please sir, apologize to her.
What?
My daughter will forgive you.
Hmm.
Sorry, kiddo.
You totally soaked me.
Idiot!
Bloody psycho.
I forgive you, sir.
- Want me to give you a smack?
- Forgive you, forgive you, forgive you.
- You are useless.
- He said sorry, baby.
- Otherwise, I would've hit him.
- Yes I saw it.
From the paddy fields of Kuttanad,
Clip-clop, clip-clop, clip-clop.
Hey little girl, you are like a cuckoo.
The golden waves of pamba river,
Came running, oh girl,
Oh my golden girl.
We need a grand welcome,
We need music playing as well.
Like a horse galloping along,
'Clip-clop, clip-clop, clip-clop.
Clip-clop, clip-clop, clip-clop.
Like a horse galloping along,
You're my baby Johnny,
Johnny, baby Johnny.
You're my baby, baby, baby Johnny.
Our story is beautiful,
In it there's a king and queen too.
You are the apple of my eye,
You are my sweetheart, it's no lie.
We're like jokers here,
Together we can do what you please, dear.
You are my...
You are my sky.
Without you I cannot survive,
Your existence is my life.
There is no one like you,
Your dad wants to shower
all his love upon you.
There is no one like you,
I love your mischievousness, too.
We got here earlier
than we did yesterday.
Good job, right?
Late! Late! Late! Again late!
Always late!
Left, right, left!
- Left, right, left!
- Bag!
- All okay, baby?
Left, right, left!
OKAY!
Hey, no cheating.
Good morning, ma'am.
Why are you late?
Miss, the bike broke down
on the way here.
Then some idiot splashed mud all over me.
So, we chased him and chased him
and chased him.
- We chased him for so long--
- Stop it, Khushi.
I just asked for the reason,
not the whole story.
Baby, bye.
Huh?
Who is he?
Oh, he... ?
He is my brother.
- Brother?
- Yes.
Start, Pinky. Pinky, start.
Is there a problem?
The poor guy's heart was shattered.
It's been a year now.
Do you have a solution, miss?
Huh?
Get in!
From the paddy fields of Kuttanad,
Clip-clop, clip-clop, clip-clop.
Hey little girl, you are like a cuckoo.
The golden waves of pamba river,
Came running, oh girl,
Oh my golden girl.
- Your order.
- one sec.
Baby, don't take money from her, please.
- Here.
- It's okay. On the house.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
We just lost 100 rupees.
Hey little girl, you are like a cuckoo.
You are my precious toy,
Your being is important
for me to survive,
Tiger!
All the happiness and joy too,
The whole wide world,
I'll bring to you.
You're my Baby Johnny, Johnny,
Baby Johnny.
You're my baby, baby, Baby Johnny.
You are the apple of my eye,
You are my sweetheart, it's no lie.
We're like jokers here,
Together we can do what you please, dear.
You are my...
You are my sky.
Without you I cannot survive,
Your existence is my life.
- There is no one like you,
- No, no, no medicine.
You are one in a million, beautiful.
- Baby...
- There is no one like you,
You can check wherever you want to.
From the paddy fields of Kuttanad,
Clip-clop, clip-clop, clip-clop.
Hey little girl, you are like a cuckoo.
The golden waves of pamba river,
Came running, oh girl,
Oh my golden girl.
- Baby, I don't love you!
- But I love you, baby.
Late! Late! Late! Again late!
- Always late! Useless!
- What's wrong, baby?
If you're always going drop me
off after two classes are over,
it'll take me three years
to finish first grade.
But baby, safety is important too, right?
- Slow and steady wins the race.
- You are only slow!
Go tell that to my teacher!
Idiot!
There was a little chicken.
Excuse me, ma'am.
You are late, again.
Baby just wouldn't wake up.
You come up with a new excuse every day.
Stand outside.
Go inside!
Oh!
Sorry, sorry, we are late.
This won't do.
I know a girl broke your heart,
but that doesn't mean you roam
around like a forlorn lover.
A girl broke your heart... ?
Get a clean shave,
you'll look handsome.
I don't know Malayalam.
Oh. Sorry.
Get a clean shave,
you'll look handsome.
- Okay, baby. Tomorrow when...
- Huh?
Sorry.
Okay, miss.
Four times four is seventeen,
right, baby?
Are you testing me?
So it's not seventeen?
- Sixteen!
- Yeah, okay, okay.
By the way,
I met your teacher yesterday at school.
Which teacher?
I didn't get a good look at her.
I mean, she had big eyes,
curly hair like Maggi noodles,
round cheeks, like a bun.
You just said you didn't get
a good look at her,
and yet you know all this.
- She is Miss Tara.
- Okay.
You should keep your interactions with
that teacher to just homework and class.
Concentrate on my homework!
Remember the peacock you drew last time?
I had to work really hard
to convince my teacher
that it was a peacock and not a camel.
You're ruining my life!
Devi! Why are you getting so upset?
We are just going out for a spin.
Huh?
Hey...
Devi!
I left in my car...
Sorry, baby.
I got held up at the bakery.
Ready to go?
Let's go.
What happened?
You know my classmate Ronnie?
- He hit me.
- Why?
He keeps teasing me
and called me bakery.
I told him my name's not bakery,
it's Khushi.
So he hit me.
So then, did you hit him?
Uh-uh.
Why, baby?
You only taught me no,
not to fight with people.
Only be kind.
- Did Ronnie say sorry to you?
- No.
He in fact laughed at me.
- He laughed at you?
- Hmm.
That is so bad, baby.
- Imagine you are in a car.
- Okay.
And there's a buffalo sitting right
in the middle of the road.
Is it small or fat?
Doesn't matter.
If you politely tell the buffalo,
Move, will it move?
No, it won't move.
Exactly, baby.
So, you'll have to give the buffalo
a solid hi-five on the back.
You've got to explain things to people
in a language they understand.
That is life, my love.
Ronnie, you idiot!
Mummy!
Mummy, I want a red balloon.
Baby, if the teacher wanted to punish us,
she would've asked us
to meet at school.
But she asked us
to meet at the church.
- Maybe she wants to forgive us.
- Hmm.
- You're so silly, baby.
- Why?
You believe anything I say.
Okay, sure.
- Okay, see you on Sunday.
- Okay.
There she is!
Your teacher is here.
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Maggi miss!
Do you teach Khushi
to fight like this, huh?
You look so innocent,
but you teach a kid violence?
Violence?
No, that's not it, ma'am.
Haven't you read the Bible?
What does the Bible say?
Bible?
Love your enemies.
Oh.
You haven't read it?
I have, I have.
But self-defense
is also important for baby.
Oh, my God! She is only five years old.
How could you...
Baby, our van!
Are you blind?
You couldn't see the car?!
- Hey, kiddo, come here!
- Huh?
Don't you have brains?
Idiot!
Which school do you go to?
School?
She should've at least said college.
- Tell me!
- This is too much.
- You buffalo!
- Baby! Hey... !
Sorry, boss. Sorry.
- You are wise beyond your years!
- Baby, stop.
- She is just a kid, sir.
- Then control her.
- Let me go.
- Yes.
- I will hit them.
- Sorry, boss. Sorry.
- She is just a kid.
- Let's go find Devi.
Khushi!
- Baby, understand no...
- You understand!
Can you give me a lift, please?
- Where do you want to go?
- Go straight.
Take a left.
Stop, stop, stop.
Police station?
- Sorry, boss. Sorry.
- You are wise beyond your years!
No! Let me go! Let me go!
Don't worry. Come with me.
Sorry, brother.
It's okay.
Miss, wait for me.
Khushi!
- Khushi!
- Watch it!
Sir!
Emergency call!
It hurts.
We'll go to the hospital after this.
Have you lost your mind?
Who gave you permission
to bring my daughter here?
Khushi...
- I didn't know that Khushi was here.
- Please stay away from us.
- What seems to be the problem?
- No.
What happened?
Tell me.
Sir, a couple of goons
were chasing this girl.
We are just here to file a report.
Sir, we'll be on our way.
Let's go, baby.
Wait a minute.
What's your name?
Sir, John D'Silva.
John.
We have met before,
in Dehradun, right?
Oh no, sir, I have never been there...
My name is John D'silva.
This is my hometown.
We run a bakery here
since the British times.
My grandfather's name
is Nicolas D'Silva,
and my father's name
is Kuruvila D'Silva.
Now, I am running it.
I don't know Malayalam.
Sir, I have no connection
to Dehradun as you mentioned.
Bye.
Come, let's go.
Satya!
- Hey Satya!
- Sir.
- Get the file.
- Okay, sir.
We've been looking
for him for so long.
It's finally time to catch him.
Let's go.
Tell me.
I found Devi.
Huh?
Well done!
One more thing.
- No, no...
- Someone has filed a complaint against you.
Damn it!
Sorry, baby.
It's not my teacher's fault.
I'm the one who ran after her.
I'm also sorry, baby.
Papa won't scold you like
this ever again.
Candy promise?
Candy promise!
Tiger!
Good boy.
Go inside.
Why are you looking up there?
Look down here.
Yes, sir.
How can I help you?
Huh?
Can I have two egg puffs
and some chutney to lick?
Sir,
- I think there's been a misunderstanding.
- Acting, huh!
Come here you!
- I didn't do anything, sir.
- Acting smart, huh?
- Pretending to sell buns...
- Sir, please listen to me!
While you actually sell our information.
- Sir, I didn't say anything, sir.
- Bloody spy!
Superb! Fantastic! Amazing!
Even IPS officers are working for us now.
You filed a complaint against us,
didn't you?
Now Mr. Rao is going to come here
to pass his judgment on you.
Where's my daughter?
Papa!
Come here.
Come here, sweetheart.
Come on.
Hey... hit him.
Sir... I really don't know, sir.
Kill this bug.
You have no idea
what Rao is capable of.
You have no idea what John can do.
Don't make me do this.
Do this.
Six years ago,
- there was a man-
- I didn't file any complaint, sir.
Hey, go get his daughter.
A devil to those who were bad,
A god to those who were good.
His name is IPS SATYA VERMA!
Baby John! Baby John!
Kill him!
Look, here comes Baby John,
I don't care when the blood drops spill,
Just another another another kill.
Look, here comes Baby John,
Baby John! Baby John!
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
A battle is brewing
and he's gonna spare none,
Here comes, Baby John!
Come on,
try and touch my daughter!
Devil gonna come better
watch your ways,
Wake up the lion and you're gonna pay,
Oh Baby John!
Bruh!
The enemies run better show your face,
Wake up the lion and you turn to prey,
Oh Baby John!
Bruh!
Don't make me do this!
You hid from us.
You faked your death!
Satya! Enough!
Just another another another kill,
I don't care when the blood drops spill,
Bruh!
You made a big mistake by killing Rao.
Now his boss will come for you.
Well, the boss
is standing right in front of you.
When you feel the fight
of the hundred man,
Whatchu gonna do then?
Bruh!
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
A battle is brewing
and he's gonna spare none,
Here comes, Baby John!
"Those dark goggles look good on you. "
- "They really suit your fair face. "
- Nice goggles!
Where'd you get them?
At the Mahim fair.
- Aarav...
- Yeah?
- Did you finish your homework?
- I did everything except English.
What about you?
Same here.
Hey, who turned the lights on?
The drunk mice are back!
Uncle, school starts today.
Come on, get up!
School's closed. Go away.
It's not closed.
It's our school. You should leave.
Come on!
You woke me up too early,
you little troublemaker!
Leave!
It's the same trouble everyday.
What should we do?
Back again, you troublemaker?
Bloody...
What's going on here?
Jai Hind, sir.
You're drinking in a public school,
and then you hit a kid?
Come on, let me
show you around the jail.
- Come with me.
- Get lost!
Brothers,
this inspector's acting like a real cop.
- Contact Sir on the wireless.
- Yeah, yeah.
Sir, some drunk guys are causing trouble
in a public school.
They hit a kid with a bottle.
They've also hurt Inspector Taawde.
Sir, you...
We need your help, sir.
Sir?
Sir isn't responding.
- Does God ever answer back?
- Uh-uh.
You've made your plea.
Your work will be done.
One, two, three.
Brothers, looks like they've sent
a tough three-star officer.
Cute.
He looks like a shorter version
of Amitabh Bachchan from Deewar.
Go, close the door.
We've got a mosquito here-squash it.
Oh, my God!
One, two, three,
Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine...
Hmm.
What's the old name of Delhi?
Easy-Old Delhi.
Correct!
Wrong answer.
It's me?
Okay!
What do we Indians celebrate
on August 15th?
I know!
Dry day.
Yes!
Come again?
Dry day.
Dry...
we can't get alcohol that day.
So, we make sure to stock up
two days before.
- Right?
- Yep, correct.
No No No!
Save me! Save me!
Sinful uncle,
come, come, come.
What's the fastest animal in the world?
Animal?
Wolf!
Who'd know that better than you, sir?
- Wrong answer?
- Hmm.
Mummy! Mummy!
Stop! Stop!
Stop, doctor, or you'll slim down!
Gunda bhai MBBS!
Was that a joke?
Come here.
No.
Hey, the miss is calling you!
- Come here, he won't hit you.
- No, no, please.
He is a good miss.
Third-grade questions won't work.
I've only gone to school
till second grade.
Can you go easy on me?
Just a little?
Nursery?
Twinkle twinkle little star,
How I wonder what you are,
Up above the world so high,
Like a diamond in the sky!
Repeat it.
- Tinkle, tinkle...
- Hmm.
Uncle!
- Super star!
- Carry on!
Wow I under what you are.
Up is sky, down is valley,
Here's my hand,
just whack me, buddy?
I made a mistake, let me go.
So what's more difficult - being a goon,
or passing the third grade?
Passing the third grade, sir.
Class dismissed.
Amazing, simply amazing!
No windows or bones were broken!
You pulled off a hero's act without
even an action sequence!
How do you do it, sir?
Satya Verma, good vibes only.
Yay!
You are a super cop, brother.
Jai Hind!
Everyone applauds loud and clear,
He's a gardener who plants tree,
Brave you must be!
Rowdy's horse runs free,
He dons the uniform fearlessly,
Brave you must be!
Come on, come on, sing with me,
All the sirs, all the stars,
feel the glee.
Come on now,
You have nothing to fear now.
Our song, play it now.
Shoot the rowdy and knock him down,
Let's play Holi
and spread the love all around.
The heartbeats rise as the rhythm flows,
Desires grow and the excitement shows,
The rest will be taken care of you know.
Security and protection is strong,
Dance, groove and have fun all night long.
Security and protection's strength,
With friends around,
the day never ends.
let's go.
Let's go.
No, sir. No, sir.
Forgive me, sir.
Brother, autograph, please.
My intentions are simple you know,
Listen my funda/message
is also very clear,
Be good and I'll be good to you,
If it's a bad guy,
the baton's for you.
Don't mistake me for a rookie,
I'm solid as rocks,
my foolish buddy,
I am honest,
smart and tough as steel,
I'm a hardcore commander, for real.
Shoot the rowdy and knock him down,
Let's play Holi
and spread the love all around.
Pay attention to my steps bro,
Keep going with the flow,
The rest will be taken care of you know.
Security and protection is strong,
Dance, groove and have fun all night long.
Security and protection's strength,
With friends around,
the day never ends.
My precious, you're gone, you've died,
Tell me,
which demon stole you from my side?
Nanaji, it won't happen again.
A body has nine openings,
and at the time of death,
the soul exits through
these nine openings.
If the life force exits
through the skull,
it is called "Kapaal Moksha. "
Only enlightened beings
are granted this opportunity.
I am god!
- Come on!
- No!
It was just a small thing.
You should've forgiven him.
You order food.
Someone works hard to make
it and sends it.
But this dog,
whose job is just to deliver it,
takes a bite and gives
you his half-eaten food.
Would you eat it?
No, right?
Just like that, I had sent a girl.
But this dog
took advantage of her before
she could reach the customer.
Scoundrel.
Tell me,
how would you feel
if you were the customer?
You wouldn't like it, right?
No, no, no.
Burning all in its way,
This lion will slay,
Like a storm it will roar,
Its thunder will soar.
Those who fall in its claws,
Will be left with no cause.
Badrinath.
He soiled your daughter, Badrinath.
And that's why I killed him.
Why are you crying, you fool?
Come on, laugh! Come on!
What happened, Badri?
Are you angry?
Come on, kill me.
Slit it.
Come on, do it.
Do it.
I am a lion.
A mighty lion!
Look, look at this,
What a mighty lion he is.
That's my father.
Bhattachari.
He was a policeman.
An honest police officer,
just like him.
Mom, I was just about
to crush the last candy.
This is the last candy for you.
After this, all your dreams
of getting married will be crushed.
The priest said
if you don't marry this girl,
there won't be another good time
for marriage for the next three years.
Then you can crush
all the candies you want.
Shall we begin then, son?
Yes, go ahead.
She's just like you.
I know you want it,
but you're never gonna get it.
You'll never get your hands on me.
Whether people believe it or not,
the world is crazy in love with me.
Mom, who still does arranged marriages
in the age of Tinder?
There should be love in a relationship.
There should be real feelings.
You've had your share
of those "feelings. "
What was her name?
Sonal?
Swati?
The prime youth of Sheila.
She sings so well!
- Uncle, I want to--
- What will he say anyway?
If I say yes, he'll say yes twice over.
Right?
That's against the law.
I'll talk to her.
Leave me, Mummy.
You're so famous!
Girls treat you like a celebrity.
And you're so cute too.
You've got such a baby face.
Thank you.
Everyone's ready
to marry me off to you.
The elders, even the kids.
But the thing is, brother...
- Brother?
- Yeah.
I've got a boyfriend,
and I want to marry him, brother.
My grandfather made my dad promise
on his deathbed
that his granddaughter will marry
a police officer.
That grumpy old man...
You tell my family
that you don't like me.
Please, brother.
- Okay, sister.
- What's my name?
What's my name?
My name is Sheila!
The prime youth of Sheila!
I'm too sexy for you!
You'll never get your hands on me.
She said yes?
No, no, no, no.
Sheila!
The prime youth of Sheila!
You'll get married only
after I die, right?
Mom, why does everything always
end up with you dying?
I don't even want to talk to you.
- Stop it.
- Mom...
- Come on, Mom.
- No.
- Mom...
- I don't want to talk to you.
Brother, please. It's just 30 rupees.
Please buy one.
Do you want to go to school?
Will you go if I get you admitted to one?
No, brother,
I don't want to go to school.
Please, buy one.
- Here.
- I don't want money, ma'am.
If you have anything to eat,
just give me that.
I'm starving. Please.
Raja!
Are you crazy?
Who are you talking to?
Sir, give him something if you want,
but please don't talk to him.
Sir, he'll hit him if he sees it.
- Sir, please, sir.
- Who's going to hit him?
He...
- Raja!
- Hey!
What are you doing here, huh?
Did I send you here just
to waste time?
I didn't do anything, boss.
He said he'd send me to school.
A school, really?
Come on, scram.
Who's this noble guy?
Do you have any idea
how many new schools you'd have to open
if you start sending everyone to school?
Why mess up the future
of upcoming businessmen?
The light's green.
Go!
Otherwise,
I'll leave you bruised and red.
See you, ma'am.
Mom, just give me five minutes.
I'll be back before
this Badshah song ends.
I'm scared, Satya.
I'll be fine, Mom.
- Not for you.
- Then?
Only for those goons.
What a cutie, Mummy!
What's your problem, man?
- You one of those human rights people?
- Uh-uh.
I have a deal with the cops.
You heard of Nanaji?
You heard of me?
Satya Verma, good vibes only.
Bugger off.
I've come across plenty like you before.
Plenty like me might
have been here before,
but this is the first time I'm here.
Run!
What's happening with India's economy?!
Darling, inflation's through the roof.
How are we supposed to manage the house?
Hello, sir.
My wife!
Police! Help!
Police!
Stop shouting "police, police, police!"
I am the police.
What happened? Accident?
No, ma'am.
- You guys hit each other?
- No, ma'am.
Then?
One guy hit all of us.
A goon?
A cop.
So, you ran away from the police
and came here?
We didn't run away from him, ma'am.
He brought us here.
Hello!
I sent you ten hearts.
You didn't even send one back.
Hey, uncle!
I'll call you back.
Yep, he's definitely a goon.
What's up, sister?
You done?
Hey, I'm not a nurse or your sister.
I'm a doctor.
Me not also uncle.
- Single.
- Hmm.
Did you do this?
Does it look like I hit them?
Sir hit them.
Then call your "sir".
Sir! Sir! The doctor's calling for you.
Why? Did one of them die?
Sir, I didn't say anything.
Hello, doctor. Beautiful day.
How can I help you?
- Take off your glasses.
- Huh?
Take off your glasses.
They're not glasses, they're shades.
- What is it?
- You hit them?
It's my job to do that, ma'am.
You think you can hit anyone just
because you're a police officer?
- They're not just anyone, ma'am. They are...
- They've lost so much blood.
You know how hard it is to get blood?
And you're breaking bones here.
It takes four months
for a single bone to heal.
Those four months are a nightmare.
You can't even go to the toilet.
You can't eat.
You need help from family
and friends for everything.
You have to take care
of them like they're kids, sir.
And what if that happens to a kid?
An orphan, with no family, no home?
What do you mean?
He broke a six-year-old's legs
and left him on the streets to beg.
He shoved a hot iron rod into
a nine-year-old's eyes
and turned her blind.
There were 14 such kids
at the signal today.
There are probably around 90 kids
in the city
who were hurt and forced to beg
by this man and his gang.
- He took advantage of innocent children--
- Sir! Sir!
Yeah, I hit them.
I didn't do anything wrong,
and I'm not going apologize
for it, ma'am.
Hmm?
Does it hurt?
As it should.
Give me your hand.
Sir, they've all be given first aid.
Brother,
the school you're sending me to-
is it a Hindi medium
or an English medium school?
Yes, brother.
I also want to go to school.
Nurse aunty said
they can fix my eye here.
Please, brother.
Ram Sevak,
take them to the children's home.
- Okay.
- Okay, kids,
I'll come by tomorrow morning
to see you all. Okay?
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Bye!
Let's go, kids!
Hi!
You can wear your glasses,
I mean, your shades.
Wow!
Are you married?
No.
Got a girlfriend?
It never worked out.
- Then okay.
- Doctor Meera,
- the Dean's calling for you.
- I'm coming!
Ask her!
What do you mean by 'okay'?
My shift ends at 8:30 PM.
Meet me after that, hmm?
Okay?
Okay!
"I'll still continue to love you. "
Hi!
Hi.
What did that "okay" mean?
"Okay" means "okay. "
You're saying "okay" again!
Ma'am, I'm the Deputy Commissioner
of this district.
DCP!
Hmm, busy man.
I'm responsible for more than half
the law and order in this city.
And I've put all that aside,
gotten on this bus,
and sat behind you
just to figure out why you said
that four-letter word, "okay. "
So why are you sitting back there?
Come sit next to me, sir.
I will, now that you've asked me to.
Meera.
- Chennai Ponnu.
- Huh?
- I'm from Chennai.
- Ah!
- I'm a house surgeon.
- Wow!
I believe the heart's main job is to send
a signal to your brain every second,
no matter what's the situation.
Wow!
That means your heart sent you
a signal when you saw me.
Okay.
But you're really beautiful.
There must be a lot of guys chasing you.
Yeah, but every guy I met,
I always got the same signal-
"no, no, no. "
But today, talking to you,
I got a different signal-a soft one.
"Okay. "
Sorry, I'm rambling about myself.
What's your story?
It's a tragic one.
I'm always surrounded by men.
First, I went to a boys' school,
then a boys' college,
and then a boys' police academy.
Hmm.
Every girl I met, I thought,
"She's the one. "
So, you've proposed to a lot of girls?
I've lost count.
I see, so you've lost count, huh?
It hurts.
Okay.
But...
I didn't know we were supposed
to get a signal from the heart.
Now you know, right?
Close your eyes,
and see what signal your heart sends you.
Hey, Romeo and Juliet,
where do you want to go?
I don't know where we're going,
but wherever we go,
we'll go together.
Dad,
this guy working at the toll booth,
earning a salary of 10,000 rupees,
told me I had to pay the toll.
No one stops these worthless guys
who wash your underwear!
Instead, people stand up
and salute them.
I'm your son,
but nobody respects me.
What do you want from me?
Dad...
Hmm?
Yeah.
Salute.
Hmm.
- A car with a red beacon on it.
- Mm-hmm.
I want to be a minister.
That's it.
Come here. Come on.
Come here.
Come.
My boy...
Alright, I'll make you one.
From today,
my son is the Finance Minister.
- Ashwin Baba!
- Long live!
My baby!
I'm so proud of you!
- Good morning, sir.
- Yes, good morning.
Let's go.
I've got a lot of work today.
Not work, trouble.
- Let's go.
- Huh?
What are you doing here, Mummy?
Chembur is on the way
to your office, right?
There's a big function
at Sapna Aunty's place today.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Please step out of the car.
- What?
- First, step out of the car.
What... what do you think, huh?
- Come on, Mummy. Come.
- Hey... !
You think I got this official car
to take my family on a picnic?
This is an official government vehicle
assigned to a government official.
All the goons, hooligans,
and drunkards can ride in it,
but your mother,
the one who carried you
in her womb for nine months,
the one who nurtured you,
sang lullabies to you-
she can't ride
in this official car of yours!
- How many times--
- You'll get an auto rickshaw at the junction.
Take that and go there.
If they refuse,
call DCP Satya Verma.
Good vibes only!
"Good vibes only!"
I'm the mother
of the Deputy Commissioner,
but I don't't even get coriander
or chilies for free!
Wait!
I knew you'd take me along.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Lal Bahadur Shastri.
Will he be riding with us too?
He was the second
Prime Minister of India!
Oh.
And his mother lived in a small house.
Learn something from her, Mummy.
Fine, so you're making fun of me, huh?
- Not at all.
- That's great.
- Mummy, I love you.
- I love you, my foot!
Mummy!
The safety of all women
is our responsibility.
King of police.
Steady, sir.
I am steady.
Hi.
Hi... hi.
Today's the first time I've worn a sari.
When I saw myself in the mirror,
I thought,
"Hmm, the sari really suits you, Meera. "
But then I didn't know who to call
to show off my beauty,
and then I remembered you.
Okay, so did you get a good look?
Bye!
Wait a second.
By the way, where are you going
to show off your beauty?
Chembur,
to attend my friend's baby shower.
And how are you getting there?
In an auto rickshaw.
Come on, Meera!
How can you go in an auto rickshaw
when I have such a big, cozy,
well-maintained car?
No!
Government vehicle?
What is government?
What is government, Ram Sevak?
Whatever you think it is, must be right.
You tell us, sir.
Government is of the people,
by the people...
For the people?
Right, Ram Sevak?
Absolutely right, sir.
- Come on, let's drop you.
- Come.
Okay, listen...
Can I bring my friends along too?
Of course, you can.
Call all your friends.
We'll make room.
There's plenty of space in our hearts-
I mean, in our car.
Come on, hurry up.
It was a game
of pretend house with dolls,
While playing the doll
didn't realize at all,
When she gave her heart
to the boy doll.
Speak with sweetness,
Think with love,
For someone special is coming soon,
my friend.
Get little toys,
A blanket from the moon,
Turn your arms into a swing,
For someone special is coming soon,
my friend.
Give me a glimpse.
Steal sweet kisses,
Sing soft lullabies,
Tie secure thread.
Through the gentle sun,
Happiness will soon shower,
With laughter blooming
like fresh flowers.
Someone is about to belong to you,
And you, too,
should belong to someone too.
What's the path that leads the way?
For someone special is coming soon,
my friend.
Give me a glimpse.
Hello!
My dear darling son!
- What are you doing here?
- I'll tell you!
- Public service, ma'am.
- Yes.
Oh, Mom!
Mummy!
Mom...
I've gone through so much trying
to find a good match for you.
But you never said yes to any girl.
- Yeah, I didn't. So...
- And now,
you've brought a girl home
from who knows where,
and you think I'm just going
to be okay with it?
Let me be clear.
Listen carefully.
I don't like her at all.
She's beautiful.
Here's her coffee...
Her cup of coffee.
Give it to her.
Once she's done, take her home.
Don't even go near her street again.
Go.
Go!
Should I leave?
Go.
In the morning,
you were so happy to give me a ride.
Why do you look so sad now?
Hmm?
I saw.
Look, my mom has a habit
of speaking her mind.
Please don't take it personally.
- It's okay. It is what it is.
- No.
Meera, sorry.
Mom can be like a kid sometimes,
but she's got a good heart.
- Please...
- It's okay, Satya.
- Go home.
- What did Mom say?
She said...
she didn't like me at all.
And there's no way
she'll let us get married.
Satya!
- If you don't like me...
I was about to say the same thing to you.
My life's been all about him
since the day he was born.
I've raised him with so much love.
I can't go against his wishes,
even if I wanted to.
And if, you know,
just in case we don't get along...
You'll take him away from me, right?
Your kids would stay away
from me as well.
Then all these 30 years of my life
will feel pointless, right?
Please don't take this the wrong way.
You never wished you had a daughter?
Of course, I did!
I always wanted a daughter!
In fact,
I've already made all the arrangements.
Clothes and everything.
But I got him instead.
Sons are good too.
And Satya is my life.
But daughters really bring life
to a home.
I don't have a mom.
I just have a dad
who loves me a lot.
But still,
sometimes I wish I had a mom.
I could've gone to her to fix my hair.
I could've shared my feelings with her.
We could've gone shopping together.
We'd bargain like crazy.
"Hey mister, I'm not paying 500,
how about 200?"
"Two for 200!"
Every time I met Satya,
he'd always talk about you.
"My mom, my baby, my darling... "
I used to wonder what kind
of darling you were.
Now I get it.
You really are a darling, Mom.
Can I call you...
My mom?
Would you like tea or coffee?
- Coffee.
- You won't get it.
I'll get it right away.
Oh!
Wow, the Deputy Commissioner has
tears in his eyes!
Meera! Meera! Meera!
What else did she say?
She asked, "When are you going
on your honeymoon?"
What?
- Woohoo!
- Heyyyy!
Hey, the warden will wake up.
O' Tantrum thrower, belong to me,
O' Sunglasses wearer, come with me.
Let's together learn the magic
of the mesmerizing the heart, come on.
Let's together learn how
to spellbound the body, come on.
You're young, and so am I,
Let the noise reach the sky.
You are mine, and I am yours,
Now, everyone knows the score.
I know it, and you do too,
Our bond is strong and true.
Now, let our eyes begin to flirt,
Let the two flirt and love,
To the heart content we flirt,
You and me for sure.
Now, let our eyes begin to flirt,
Let the two flirt and love,
To the heart content we flirt,
You and me for sure.
Young beauty, you're pure gold,
Let me make turn you into ring, girl.
The language of your eyes is right,
But your lips tell only lies.
Half of my promises are sincere,
The rest will be too in time, my dear,
Together, we'll savor each delight,
Sweet and sour through the night.
Now, I will be where you go,
Wherever your kohl glows.
Now, let our eyes begin to flirt,
Let the two flirt and love,
To the heart content we flirt,
You and me for sure.
Now, let our eyes begin to flirt,
Let the two flirt and love,
To the heart content we flirt,
You and me for sure.
O' Tantrum thrower, belong to me,
O' Sunglasses wearer, come with me.
Let's together learn how
to entice the mind, come on.
Come, let's go.
Thaman Bhai, once more.
Come on!
- Sir, tea.
- Sir, your mom said
you should eat your meal
and not make a fuss.
- Put it in your mouth--
- Hey!
Kali, who are these people?
They've been here for
about an hour, sir.
- I've already filed their report.
- Send them in.
Okay.
Go ahead, tell me.
My daughter's name is Amba, sir.
She's in tenth grade.
Three days ago,
she left for school but...
never came back.
So, your daughter's been missing
for three days.
Did you file a report
at the nearest police station?
Yes, we went there, sir.
We paid them 10,000 rupees.
They promised they would find her.
But yesterday,
when we went to ask about her,
they told us
she ran away with someone.
Our daughter wouldn't do that, sir.
They are lying, sir.
You...
you are our only hope, sir.
Please, find our daughter.
Forward, forward, forward... stop.
Go back, go back, go back.
Did Amba get into
any fights at school?
No, sir.
She's a very sweet and innocent girl.
Sir, I found some important footage.
Here, take a look at this.
- Excuse me, sir?
- Yes?
Have you seen this girl?
Yes, this girl gets off
at this bus stop every day
and then goes this way.
What's wrong with this dog?
This dog's been acting crazy because this
girl hasn't been here since three days.
She used to buy biscuits
from my shop on her way to
and from school and feed him.
That's why he'd always
follow her around.
Let's go, Ram Sevak.
Get the dog into the car too.
Why, sir?
Dogs have a peculiar instinct.
They never forget anything,
especially if they were close to someone,
and that someone was hurt
by someone else.
Like this dog,
who's been chasing
only big cars.
That means Amba was hurt by someone
who drives a big car.
Don't worry, Amba will be fine.
Stop, stop, stop.
Get the footage
from the last three days.
Yes, sir.
Pause whenever you see a Jeep.
Okay, sir.
Forward.
Okay, pause, pause.
Zoom in.
That's it.
- Give me a printout of that car.
- Okay, sir.
- Let's go.
Where's the next ATM on this road?
There's a forest up ahead.
There might not be
any ATMs further along.
There's an industrial estate
about six kilometers ahead.
There could be an ATM there, sir.
I've checked the footage
from the past three days, sir.
No black jeep
has passed through here yet.
Here.
This means Amba
is somewhere within
this six-kilometer radius.
Yes.
If we find the black jeep...
- We find Amba.
- Correct.
Alert the neighboring police stations.
Okay, sir.
Yes, sir.
Copy, sir.
- Cordon off the entire area.
- Take your helmet off.
Come on, sir!
Move it.
I want complete surveillance.
Sir is checking.
Also alert the medical team
and the ambulance.
We don't have much time.
We have to find her.
Stop, stop, stop.
Let me go! Let go of me!
My child!
Amba!
Patil, you check this side.
You two, go that side.
Come on, come on!
Amba!
Bye!
You've gotten all dirty, darling.
Brother!
Hey!
My child!
Amba!
O' my moon, O' my precious one,
- What an unfair farewell this is.
- Brother!
The one I cherished like
a delicate flower every day,
Why has she withered away?
With my veil,
I shielded you from the sun,
But I couldn't save you today,
Though, you called out my name.
Now your ashes question me -
What was my fault tell me.
I screamed and cried,
I am being punished, tell me why!
Bhaiya, my books..
My eyes have run dry,
Silence consumes me,
How can any leave you
and just walk away?
- My child!
- My eyes have run dry,
Silence consumes me,
How can any leave you
and just walk away?
Satya, I'm sorry.
We could've saved her.
Her body had only 40% burns, but...
Doctor...
Look at her father's eyes.
How do I tell him
his daughter
won't be going home with him?
How do I say that to him?
I'm sorry.
You can't speak or hear,
but at least you can see, right?
Can't you see?
They killed our daughter!
They killed her!
They killed Amba!
It's over!
It's all over! Amba!
Her leg bones are broken too.
And her intestines
are severely damaged as well.
It looks like an iron rod was inserted.
O' my moon, O' my precious one,
The courtyard will weep in silence.
How will your father sleep
now that you're gone?
You once sat on my shoulders,
Swinging your legs so freely,
I was my father's joy,
You would proud say it with glee.
Now my dreams are shattered,
Just wait and see,
I'm going to grow up and make you proud.
Brother!
My eyes have run dry,
Silence consumes me,
How can any leave you
and just walk away?
My eyes have run dry,
Silence consumes me,
How can any leave you
and just walk away?
Long live Ashwin Baba!
Don't worry, sir.
- We'll do our best on our end to-
- Sir.
Satya?
What are you doing here?
What happened?
Sir, we are here to arrest his son.
What?
On the charges of raping
and murdering a little girl.
Nanaji, please call your son.
- Well done, Ashwin Baba!
- Satya, do you even know who he is?
Where is he?
Breaking news!
We've just received an update
Ashwin has won with 800,000 votes.
I'm telling the truth.
We've been looking for him too,
for the past three days.
He must've partied hard
and gone to sleep.
Yes, he's right, Satya.
That's why he called me here.
Actually, I've asked Baldev's team
to look for Ashwin, unofficially.
Okay, sir.
DCP sir,
salute...
It's important to salute.
Next time you see your minister,
you should salute him.
Long live Ashwin Baba!
- Ram Sevak, stop the car.
- Hmm.
What do we do now?
What, sir?
You are asking me, sir?
Sir, you're the Deputy Commissioner.
If you can't do anything,
what can I do? I'm just a constable.
We've got the evidence.
We could take it to court.
We can arrest him.
Don't joke, sir.
Excuse me for a moment.
Take a look at this.
This is a news report that
was published last week.
Last year, there were 33,000
rape cases reported in India.
That's 93 girls every day.
That's 4 girls like Amba, every hour.
Even now, at this very moment,
some scumbag is probably
assaulting an innocent girl.
Sir, just thinking about
it makes my blood boil.
These are the cases that were
actually reported to the police.
Who knows how many more there are
that people don't report
because of shame?
Half of them get swept
under the rug like this.
This is the state our country is in.
He has an influential father.
What's the point of arresting him?
In just ten days,
he'll be out of prison,
smile at us, and walk away.
And we'll be transferred, sir.
They'll assign us to some
minister's security.
And this news... ?
It'll be in the media
for 2-3 days, max.
Then, it'll be followed by some huge
controversy over an actress's bikini
then a big wedding,
and then everyone
will forget about it.
Meanwhile,
that poor girl's father
will live with the pain
of losing his daughter
until his last breath,
suffocating in grief.
And this scumbag?
Without fear,
he'll go after another girl.
Poor don't hold any value
in this country.
If I've crossed the line, then...
You are right.
Now, imagine you're not
a police officer,
just an ordinary man.
And you get your hands
on that scumbag.
What would you do?
I'd break his jaw, sir.
I'd throw him on a pile of hay
and set it on fire.
Sir, sorry. Sir, I'll...
Sir, I'll throw it. Sorry, sir.
Just another another another kill.
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
He'll paint the world with
a crimson hue,
Turning to ashes the remaining few.
Death stands before them,
the game is on.
They'll turn to dust
as here comes Baby John!
- Why?
- What do you mean, "why"?
Because I could.
Devil gonna come better watch your ways,
Wake up the lion and you're gonna pay,
What are you doing, sir?
His father told me to salute him.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Wake up the lion and you turn to prey,
Oh Baby John! Oh Baby John!
Call his father.
The identities of the bodies
haven't been revealed.
Does the police have
a special reason to do so?
Send all the evidence from the crime scene
to the evidence room.
- Okay, sir. I'll send them right away.
- Send all the bodies
- for post-mortem.
- It'll be done, sir.
Go.
- Welcome, sir.
- DCP sir.
Good to see you found my son.
I'd like to speak with him.
You can take him to jail after that.
You want to talk to your son?
Kali!
This way, please.
Oh no! That's Nanaji's son, Ashwin!
Ashwin!
It's me, Ashwin! Please say something!
- Satya?
- Yes?
- Yes, doctor?
- Sign here.
Did you find anything
the body examination?
It's a case of brutal murder.
Here.
All five of them were killed
in the same way.
Their jaws were broken using an iron rod.
They were tortured nonstop for 2-3 days.
Anything else?
Their private parts were
also chopped off.
Most likely, they were burnt alive.
But their faces were covered
with something,
probably to make it easier
for us to identify the bodies.
- Completely psychotic behavior.
- Yeah.
We will know the rest after the autopsy.
Thank you, doctor.
Sorry, sir. I didn't notice you, sir.
Sorry, sir. Sorry...
He was...
he was my son.
I don't...
I don't understand any of this.
This is not...
This is not right.
I am not like this..
He was right here.
And now he is not.
Do me a favor.
If you don't find his name,
then anything
Give me the name of the culprit.
Anyone you suspect.
His kids, parents, siblings..
I'll set the whole world on fire!
Your son was no saint, sir.
He was an accused.
A rapist, a murderer.
Anyone could've killed him, sir.
It could've been a common man,
or someone from the press.
It could've been that girl's mother,
or her father.
Or maybe her brother.
Anything's possible, sir.
It could also be that the girl's brother
is a police officer,
whose name is IPS SATYA VERMA!
Do one thing,
call your relatives, sir,
and make arrangements for his funeral.
Scumbag!
I don't care when the blood drops spill,
Just another another another kill,
Here comes, Baby John!
Baby, where are you?
Baby?
Baby, where did you go,
- leaving me all alone?
- I was right here, baby.
Where could I go, leaving you?
I love you.
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
Death stands before them,
the game is on.
They'll turn to dust
as here comes Baby John!
Ram Sevak!
Yes sir.
One body is missing.
"Whenever and wherever
there is a decline in righteousness... "
Whenever and wherever there is
a predominance of unrighteousness,
Mummy!
To protect the righteousness...
a girl arrives.
Adhira! Adhira! Adhira!
Like an ant,
she discreetly sneaks into the ear
of an elephant
to bring it down.
There was a queen...
Come, come, come...
- Daddy!
- Come here, sweetheart.
I love you.
Get all 40 girls to the freezer yard
in Allapuzha tomorrow.
I'll give you the rest
of the details later.
Hey! What's your deal, huh?
Enjoy.
Do you know who that girl is?
The 45 girls who were kidnapped by
Rao's gang were rescued by us.
We've arrested a man who's said
to be one of Rao's close associates.
What's your name?
BOSS!
Hey!
No... it's Babloo.
We've got the tail end
of the snake now.
Soon, we'll pull the whole snake out
and crush its head.
- Hey! Jackie!
- Please leave.
Jackie...
I know who you are.
Please.
There are already
so many problems here.
We don't need any more.
- Please go.
- Ram...
I didn't do it on purpose.
I care about Satya and Khushi too,
just like you.
Please, Ram.
What happened to Meera?
And whose daughter is Khushi?
Please, tell me.
Satya, we're going
to meet a really important person.
I'm a little stressed.
Who?
Father!
Church Father?
My father!
Father-in-law?
Meera, you should've told me earlier.
Okay, what does he like and not like?
Hey, he is a very easy going guy.
There's only one thing he doesn't like.
What?
Police!
Come.
- Satya...
- Thank you.
- My aunt.
- Hello.
- Pallavi.
- Hi.
Um, hi.
My dad.
Hello, sir.
I've heard so many good things
about you.
You seem like you come
from a good family.
You look good too.
But sir, I don't like you.
You are a police officer.
It's a very risky job.
It's not like only you're going
to be the one firing the gun.
Someday, you could get hit too.
- Got it?
- Dad!
I don't want to see
my daughter cry all her life.
- Sir, when you--
- Please, forgive us.
He thinks life's a joke.
Sir, but I love her, sir.
What love, huh?
Brother, please...
What do you know
about my daughter, huh?
What makes her happy
and what makes her sad?
Love! Huh!
You are right, sir.
I don't know anything.
But do you know
why Meera became a doctor, sir?
She was the state topper!
Topper!
What would she be if not a doctor?
Sir, do you know
when Meera's mom passed,
she saw you talking to the doctor?
The way the doctor held your hand
and said,
"Sorry, sir, we couldn't save your wife, "
your 5-year-old daughter decided right
then that when she grows up,
she'll be a doctor
to save lives and make sure
no one else like you sheds tears.
Sir, sir, sir... sorry, sir.
I don't know
if I can take care of her better than you,
but I won't fall short either.
I promise you that.
And I don't just want her,
I want all of you.
The whole family, sir.
Full.
I always wanted a younger sister, sir.
Just like Pallavi.
- Pallavi?
- Yes?
I'll take you to school from tomorrow.
And if any of the boys bother you,
we'll chase them off
with our siren-equipped van.
Okay, brother.
- Aunty?
- Yes?
I've heard you make amazing Dum Aloo.
Hey...
So, I'll send you chicken curry
in a tiffin,
and you send me back Dum Aloo.
Yes, okay.
Sir, I think we should start morning walks
after I get married.
Good for the heart, sir.
And at night we'll have...
We'll have tea, sir,
and read the newspaper.
I read The Times, sir. And you?
Twitter.
Superb, sir.
I mean, who reads newspapers
these days?
Yeah.
Sir...
I don't have a father.
So, I want you to guide me, sir.
Sir, we're together
because we love each other.
But marriage...
marriage happens
when two families become one, sir.
You still don't trust me, sir?
No, I know.
Sir, I last used this during my training.
I still get scared even
of firecrackers, sir.
I'm a police officer who follows
the principles of Mahatma Gandhi, sir.
IPS Satya Verma.
Good vibes only.
Okay, you've said enough.
Drink your coffee now, son.
Thank you, sir.
He's a good guy.
Yes.
Move! Move!
Dad!
- Go, go! Go inside!
- Satya!
Hey, stop it.
Sir, you continue.
See you, crybaby.
Let's go.
Dad!
Dad! Satya!
See, this is what I've been
talking about.
Hurry up.
Come, now.
Why are you looking at him?
We made it out alive,
isn't that enough for you?
Let's go!
- Dad!
- Meera...
[CHANTS]
- Look at the crowd, sir.
- Long live Ashwin baba.
He's the one!
Burn him!
Burn them, Burn them.
Hello.
Hey!
How dare you come here?
Hey brother,
I'm here to arrest someone.
What do you think?
You can just take
Brother Bhima away that easily?
You're mistaken.
I've come to arrest him.
Someone filed a complaint
against Brother?
Who's the brave one who did that?
See Nanaji,
my hand isn't shaking now.
You know what real power is?
It's the kind of power
that empowers the weak.
- Hey!
- You rascal! How dare you!
Brother!
- Look, here comes Baby John,
- Move back. Move back.
Hey!
What?
- Ram Sevak!
- Yes, sir.
- Bring the jeep.
- They burnt the jeep, sir.
Damn it! Your men are so dumb.
Now how's Nanaji going
to leave in his shorts?
And there are so many ladies watching.
What are they going to say?
Shame, shame, puppy shame.
Shame, shame.
Nanaji, you see, you are not a lion.
You're an eagle.
That too an old eagle.
Come on!
Nanaji! Nanaji! Nanaji!
I've spoken to the lawyer.
These are the bail papers,
please sign them.
We'll get you out today itself.
Yes, Nanaji.
Brother?
Brother!
Meera!
Are you avoiding me?
This isn't right.
What isn't right?
Our life, Satya!
You roaming around like a superhero
might be good for the city,
but it's not good for your family.
Okay.
I understand that you got scared.
Of course, Satya,
I got scared.
And when he shot at you,
I was scared.
- Meera, please.
- And not just me,
Dad, Pallavi,
Aunty, everyone got scared.
I can't afford to lose you, Satya.
You won't, Meera.
Damn it, so what should I do?
What do you want me to do?
I don't know!
Leave the police force,
and we'll get married right away.
And if you can't leave your job,
then at least call an
auto-rickshaw for me.
Leave!
One
Two
Three...
You are trying to get rid of me?!
- Hey, I'm the DCP--
- How dare you?!
I'll break your face!
Okay, okay, okay!
I knew you'd come back.
But I didn't know you'd come back so fast.
Okay, listen...
I love my uniform
as much as I love you.
I'll never leave you
because of my work,
and I'll never lose
my work because of you.
Will you always be with me?
Till my last breath.
Close to me,
My destiny, you're meant
to be with me.
Through every trial and strife,
Through every twist of life,
You were meant to think of me,
all the time.
From the moment I fell for you,
I felt like I was born anew.
Once empty,
now I'm full of your thoughts,
No one like you
in this world throughout .
Oh, my angel,
Our future shines so bright,
Our future's full of light.
Our future gleams with might,
Our future burns so bright.
Sukhadaanvitha sukrutham gandham
dharmaangam preemadhara
sukhadaanvesham
madhuraathara madhumakarandham
maangalyam sumahora supadham
cha subham
kalyanam kamaneeyam
subha sakhyam ithi gamyam
madhuryam makarandham
vadhu varyam sukhamasyam
sneham cha sthira keerthyanvitha
daampatyoh sukhavardhanam
Where the sun shines,
I'll be your shadow,
Where you call,
I'll be there, you know.
I cherish you with love so true,
With you, my home feels like
a heaven's view.
Oh, my angel,
Our future shines so bright,
Our future's full of light.
Our future gleams with might,
Our future burns so bright.
Close to me,
My destiny, you're meant
to be with me.
Through every trial and strife,
Through every twist of life,
You were meant to think of me,
all the time.
- Who's my baby?
- Mom!
Hey!
Hi, baby.
- Hi, baby!
- What's up, baby?
You seem really happy today.
Hmm.
I feel complete today.
Really?
What made you feel this way?
- A realization.
- I see.
It just realized that...
I have everything.
A loving husband,
a mother-in-law
who's like a mother to me,
and a sweet, angelic daughter.
What more could a girl ask for?
So... I feel complete.
I came here all excited
to give Khushi a little brother,
and you're already complete?
Oh!
Oh, my baby! Oh, my baby!
Meera, her clothes are all dirty,
there's cake all over. I'll bathe her.
- Mom, I'll come too.
- No, no, no.
You guys rest.
Rest well, okay?
She's not ready.
Who wants a little brother?
Who wants one?
Our baby wants a little brother!
See, even the baby wants it.
Not interested.
I'm happy with Khushi.
Thank you.
Okay, ma'am.
Alright, I have a question.
No--
Hey!
See, I know you don't like me
working for the police force,
but you've made my life yours
without complaining.
But you must have a plan
of your own too, right?
Is there something you would like to do?
Tell me... tell me!
I do.
But you won't be able to fulfill it.
Try me.
Okay.
We move to a small village,
somewhere far away.
Hmm.
Your work will be such that
for twenty hours out of twenty-four,
you'll be with me.
Hmm.
We'll talk to each other all day long.
And there should be
birds chirping around the house.
And a little puppy too.
- Hmm?
- Hmm!
- I've even thought of a name for it.
- Really?
Tiger!
Is that all you dream of?
Hmm.
Okay, tell me,
what kind of wife am I?
Hmm.
You are my...
Okay...
Grandpa is coming!
"My sweetheart... "
Oh, who could it be?
Hello, ma'am!
Come on, I was talking to her.
Why did you shoot her?
Sorry, brother.
Please forgive me.
Ma'am... ?
Did she die?
Look what I brought for you - a boat!
Satya...
Satya... get up.
You killed my son.
You dragged me down the road, naked.
And what did you call me?
Ah yes, an old eagle.
Whose wings get heavy.
Whose beak is useless,
and can't hunt anymore.
But you don't know something...
Among thousands,
there's one eagle that refuses to die.
It breaks itself, sheds its old wings...
hungry, naked, it waits for 150 days.
And when it flies again,
it's no ordinary eagle.
It becomes the king of eagles.
Now, it doesn't hunt just for food.
It hunts to show its power
to the world.
In these three years in jail,
I chanted only one name
Satya. Satya. Satya.
And now, it's all over.
I'm truly happy.
Blissfully happy.
I feel complete.
My enemy is finished.
And my son is already died.
So what should I do now?
I want to go back to jail.
Brother...
Satya...
Khushi... ?
Mom...
Khushi!
Satya!
Satya...
Satya... get up, Satya.
Get up.
The hospital is
just fifteen minutes away.
Take Khushi there quickly.
Satya... Satya!
Take Khushi there, hurry up.
Satya, make me a promise.
Promise me
that you'll leave the police force,
go far away from here,
and you'll make sure nothing
happens to Khushi.
Promise me.
Satya...
You didn't answer my question
What kind of wife am I?
You're not just my wife,
you're like another mother to me!
Meera? Let's go!
Let's go, Meera! Let's go!
Satya Verma died six years ago.
Now, all I want is for John
to have a life with Khushi.
That's all I pray for.
Miss!
You are here!
Baby, put me down.
Put me down.
Miss! Miss!
We're going somewhere.
Can you come with us, please?
Wherever you go,
I'll go with you, okay?
Okay.
Shame, shame, puppy shame,
the baby is crying.
Can I join you on the trip?
It's a school trip, baby.
Only kids are allowed.
Just because I call you 'baby'
doesn't mean you're a baby.
Okay, okay, my dear.
Take care of yourself.
I won't.
Don't stick your hand out of the window.
I will.
Don't talk to strangers.
I'll miss you, baby.
I'll miss you double, baby.
Hey, the bus has come... let's go!
- Hi, Khushi!
- Hi, Ronnie!
Be careful, Khushi.
Careful, baby.
Come, come, come...
sit here, sit here.
Khushi, be careful with Ronnie, okay?
Hmm... Okay!
Take care of yourself, baby.
I'll take care of her, uncle.
Call your dad "uncle"!
Get your hand off her!
- Baby, go and sit behind.
- Okay!
Ronnie, don't be a player, okay?
Sorry, uncle!
- Yes!
- Bye, baby!
Nanaji! Nanaji! Nanaji!
How are you, Satya?
You've come back!
Now, the real fun begins!
You bloody...
How dare you come to the jail
and threaten Nanaji like that!
Let's kill him!
I'm a lion! A mighty lion!
I've got a gift for you.
Look behind you!
NOOO!
BABY!!!
Khushi!
No!
Please, help!
Help!
[Crowd chatter]
Help! Help!
Mummy!
Papa!!
[Crowd chatter]
Help!!
Khushi!
Get up, baby! Get up, baby!
Get up, baby!
Get out of the way! Move, move!
Get out of the way!
Don't worry he will be fine.
Doctor! Doctor!
Go, go, go!
My son!?
Ronnie!
I will see.
Get out of my way!
Move! Move! Move!
Hurry up.
Khushi...
Where is baby?
- My Ronnie...
- Ronnie... ?
Yes, yes, bring him here.
Doctor, check his pulse.
Leave me. My son.. Ronnie
Ronnie!
Ronnie.
Move! Move! Move!
Nurse, 250!
Baby...
Baby, Khushi's fine.
Baby, I told you, Khushi's fine.
Our Khushi is fine.
But today, because of me,
all these kids' lives were in danger.
It's all because of me.
Uncle...
Yes, Ronnie?
Is Khushi fine?
I'll never trouble Khushi again.
Come on, Satya,
I just gave my granddaughter a bath,
and you got so scared?
Now what?
Are you going to file a complaint?
But under whose name?
John or Satya Verma?
My followers give offerings
on your death anniversary.
Don't ruin it.
I'm coming, Satya Verma.
What was that demon saying?
He was saying he wants
to meet the real demon.
Sir...
The only thing left with me is
this Mangalsutra (wedding necklace) now.
It's been three weeks since
my daughter disappeared.
You promised you'd find her.
Sir...
Take this.
My daughter...
What is this?
Remove "Missing"
and print "Tribute" on it instead. Go.
Sir!
What should I do?
She keeps saying, "Sir! Sir! Sir!"!
Is your daughter some big shot that
I should set up check posts
all around the country for her?
Sir...
No matter what anyone says, to me,
my daughter is my queen, sir.
Like hell she's a queen!
Your queen is nothing
but a worthless worm!
Go away! Leave!
What happened?
He's saying my daughter's dead.
- Turn on the generator, Kali!
- Yes, sir!
Bajrang Bali!
You alone can do something now!
Come and punish these sinners!
Come! Come --
Aye!
Who is it?
The ghost has taken over
what kills you now - Bhayam!
He creeps onto your shoulder
won't leave you now - Bhayam!
What justice is this.
So many innocent kids are dying,
but this monster just refuses to die!
Kali!
Sir!
A cup of black tea with lemon.
Make it fast.
Sir!
Kali!
Hey...
BALDEV!
Yes?
Baldev...
Why are you trying to scare me, Kali?
Baldev!
Who is it?
[CHANTS]
Kali!
Yes, sir?
Take all of this and hand it back
to the rightful owners.
Sir, if Baldev sir finds out,
he'll kill me.
How can I do that, sir?
Please, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
- Any leads?
- No, sir.
Where is he?
Over there, sir.
Hey, come here.
So an Assistant Commissioner
was murdered,
Yes, sir.
and that too inside a police station.
When even the police aren't safe
inside their own station,
how are they supposed
to protect the people?
The people and the media are saying
that and blaming us for this.
Of course, sir, they will.
Who killed Baldev?
IPS Satya Verma, sir.
IPS Satya Verma died five years ago.
He was dead,
but he's alive now, sir.
- Oh.
- Yes.
I swear on my wife, sir.
You don't believe me, sir?
I swear on your wife, sir.
He killed him.
Hundred percent, sir.
Case closed.
Get him admitted to a mental hospital.
- Sir! Sir!
No comments, please.
So, is Satya Verma alive?
Or was it his ghost?
People are saying that DCP Baldev Patil
wasn't killed by an ordinary person,
but by the ghost of IPS Satya Verma.
Yes, a ghost.
For the last six years,
we've been collecting every dirty
thing we can on Nanaji.
- Satya Verma has come back now.
- Wow!
Yes, I saw.
The car passed like grrr...
And he has done a lot
for women's safety too.
"He creeps onto your shoulder
won't leave you now - Bhayam!"
- A stranger...
- From Nanaji's godown...
...found 30 kidnapped girls.
He's not a ghost, he's a god.
He's here to protect us.
Aye!
The ghost has taken over
what kills you now - Bhayam!
He creeps onto your shoulder
A mighty lion?
No way, Nanaji is a coward
Jee Boom Ba!
Runner, runner, runner,
No one is safe.
Demons, they must behave.
He's brought down Nanaji's empire.
I want to be a supercop like Satya Verma.
The police has won our hearts.
I can feel Satya Verma's presence
everywhere.
Oh Baby, it's you!
- You're a superhero! Yay!
- They city has got a new vigilante.
Brother! Brother! It's over, brother!
DCP Satya Verma is alive.
People are saying he's the one
who killed Brother Baldev.
God! Bajrang Bali!
Protector of women in this country! -
They've given him so many names.
What do we do now, brother?
You're the devil
and I'm the god,
just have faith in me.
Satya won't return.
And the one who killed Baldev,
by tonight, he too will be...
Okay, brother.
Bhima... ?
Yes, brother?
Go.
We won't start working until
you put up a safety net!
- What's going on here?
- Eight people died yesterday, sir.
Because of our faulty safety net.
Hmm.
Who's the contractor?
- Contractor!
- Yes, sir!
- Come here.
- Yes?
Come, come, come.
Eight people are dead.
I'll give eight lakh rupees
for eight people.
One lakh each.
This isn't about money, sir.
Come on, contractor,
they're just laborers.
They have no names or families.
Fine, I'll bump it up to 10 lakhs.
A round figure.
I know you won't be giving
them all the money.
Right? Right?
You can keep it.
I've spoken to Bhima sir.
He's agreed to all your demands.
Now, all of you should start working.
- Go, go, go.
Whose child is that?
His mother is dead, sir.
Don't worry, kid.
Grow up and start working.
- Sir, sir...
- Yes?
He doesn't understand Hindi, sir.
- He's from the North-East.
- I see.
No matter if it's North or South,
everyone understands THIS language.
Oh, look at that.
Here you go.
Get yourself a chocolate, okay?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Beyond your doorstep,
- Come, my king.
Boss,
two girls from the shipment
we sent last time ended up slitting
their throats and dying.
neither the world nor faith exists.
- Go on, have some. - Where do I go?
Go on, they're quite tasty.
Have some.
Quiet!
What was that noise?
Go check it out.
Okay, boss.
Raju!
Jee Boom Ba!
The ghost has taken over
what kills you now - Bhayam!
He creeps onto your shoulder
won't leave you now - Bhayam!
Nanaji, Satya Verma is alive.
He's going to kill me!
You need to leave! Run away!
Don't kill me! Don't kill me!
You can take everything! Take it all!
Just let me go.
Please, let me go.
Let me go.
Alright, I'll let you go.
- What happened?
'Get yourself a chocolate, okay?'
'Get yourself a chocolate. '
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
A battle is brewing
and he's gonna spare none,
Here comes, Baby John!
Yes, sir?
Bhima is sending his
next shipment on Sunday.
You need to catch him.
Done, sir.
Adhira Verman IPS
Hey, comedy, move aside.
You know, comedy is serious business.
Rap song
Don't come any closer.
I'm not dead!
Revenge demands sacrifice.
I sacrificed my brother
so I could turn you to ashes.
I had already left, Satya,
but you're the one
who dragged me back from prison.
Turmeric has cooled
my body on the outside,
but I'll need your blood
to cool my heart.
Come to the harbor!
Miss miss, please wake up.
Miss, I am here. Wake up.
You made it with two minutes to spare.
I'm truly happy.
Blissfully happy.
This is between us.
Give me my daughter back.
Mandar, my child, who am I?
God.
Is this how anyone asks God
for something?
Let my daughter go.
Please, let my daughter go.
I can't stand seeing him cry.
Turn the lights off. Turn them off.
It's so difficult to be God.
I swear on my mother,
I don't know which container has the girl
and which has the wood.
Only Bhima knows.
Wait, let me ask Bhima.
Bhima!
Hey Bhima!
- What?
I can't hear him.
He's too far away.
Can you do me a favor
and go ask him?
I'm an old eagle,
I can't fly that high.
Guys, help him out.
Send him up there.
Sister, please, don't cry.
My dad always says,
a lone ant can be easily crushed,
but if all the ants unite,
they can bring down an elephant.
This is the final horn.
After this, the ship will leave.
Twinkle, twinkle little star,
your daughter will be across the sea,
traveling far.
Jee Boom Ba!
Baby, it hurts.
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
Finish him.
I've had enough of this.
Satya...
Khushi!
I don't care when the blood drops spill,
Just another another another kill.
Devil gonna come better watch your ways,
Wake up the lion and you're gonna pay,
Oh Baby John!
I don't care when the blood drops spill,
Just another another another kill.
You have no idea
what it's like to lose your son.
The enemies run better show your face,
Wake up the lion and you turn to prey,
Oh Baby John!
"Say it!"
[CHANTS]
The ghost has taken over
what kills you now - Bhayam!
Rakkassaa - he's a renegade!
You won't live to see another day.
Rakkassaa - rising back from the grave!
He'll make you pay.
Runner, runner, runner,
No one is safe.
He'll take you straight to the grave.
The ghost has taken over
what kills you now - Bhayam!
Ghost on the loose,
He's a cold blooded killer.
It ain't old news
that this danger's a thriller.
Moves in the shadow,
Gets high of your fear.
"Say it!"
Say it!
[CHANTS]
Baby, I want to talk to him.
Please?
Grandpa!
Grandpa, I know everything.
If you hadn't been like this,
then my mom and baby's mom
would still be with me.
I know, I know
they're not here because of you.
Grandpa, don't be scared, okay?
My dad always says that
if someone makes a mistake,
admits it, and apologizes,
you should forgive them.
Just say sorry,
and my dad will forgive you.
A lion...
a mighty lion.
What are you saying, stupid lion?
Baby, he doesn't understand.
Talk to him in the language
he understands best.
My daughter knows
you killed her mother,
yet she still says I should forgive you.
You knew your son raped
and murdered a little girl,
yet you supported him.
A child goes astray
when they aren't raised right.
That's why I'm not responsible
for your son's death - you are.
Got it?
Actually, I should have killed you along
with your son.
But raising my daughter right
was more important
than seeking revenge on you.
And for that, you can call me
a coward, a chicken,
or whatever you want.
But today, a father has won,
and I'm truly happy about it.
Blissfully happy.
Kill me.
Otherwise, I'll come after you,
to hunt you down.
I've come across plenty like you before.
Plenty like me might
have been here before,
but this is the first time I'm here.
"Say it!"
[CHANTS]
Our next item up for bid includes
this fine specimen.
Take a good look, gentlemen.
Five million dollars!
- Ten million dollars!
- Ten million dollars!!
Sold!
Pack them all up!
Let's have some fun.
Gentlemen, our whole network
in India is finished.
We can't get any new girls.
The ghost gang is behind it.
And their leader is... Satya Verma.
Sir,
there's one more member.
And he's the worst of them all.
Bring him
Who dares to call
for their own death like this, stupid?
Get him.
Who are you?
Look, this is the face of your death.
This is the last face you will see
before going to hell.
If he's on his knees,
know that he's doing it by choice.
Oh.
Let's see.
Hit him.
Rap song
- Listen...
- Yeah?
I'm Baby John.
He's Bhai Jaan.
We've come here
to teach everyone a lesson,
and we'll leave only
after we take everyone's-
Hey!
Life.
He knows me.
You don't know me.
But you will,
just before you lose your life.
Please do the honors.
Come back a better man.
Now go.
Baby?
Yes, Bhai?
Not you, this baby.
Is she your baby?
Too late.
Bomb... !
It's remote.
Bhai...
When will you grow up, baby?
I hope that happens
before I become a father.
Well, it depends on
when you become a father.
Hey, it's not in my hands.
Then whose hands is it in?
Eid, Diwali, Holi...
Christmas!
I'll be ready by Christmas.
That means, before I become a father.
Good.
Christmas will only be fun
if you are with me, Bhai.
Let me think about it.
Done.
Merry Christmas.
Happy New Year!
Happy Ganesh Chaturthi!
Happy Eid!
Happy Diwali!
Happy Mahashivratri!
Happy Pogal!
Happy Dussehra!
Happy Basant Panchami!
Happy Janmashtami!
Onam! Happy Onam!
Happy Bihu!
Happy Durga Puja!
Happy Baisakhi!
Happy Easter!
Happy Navratri!
Happy Raksha Bandhan!
Happy, happy...
Happy Today!
Happy Tonight!
Devil gonna come better watch your ways,
Wake up the lion and you're gonna pay,
Oh Baby John!
Bruh!
Rap song
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
A battle is brewing
and he's gonna spare none,
Here comes, Baby John!
He'll paint the world with
a crimson hue,
Turning to ashes the remaining few.
Death stands before them,
the game is on.
They'll turn to dust
as here comes Baby John!
Rap song
Look, here comes Baby John,
Bruh!
Devil gonna come better watch your ways,
Wake up the lion and you're gonna pay,
Oh Baby John!
Bruh!
The enemies run better show your face,
Wake up the lion and you turn to prey,
Oh Baby John!
Rap song
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
A battle is brewing
and he's gonna spare none,
Here comes, Baby John!
Look, here comes Baby John,
He's gonna tear apart everyone,
A battle is brewing
and he's gonna spare none,
Here comes, Baby John!
Rap song